Guide to the Lesbian and Gay Liberation Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Lesbian and gay liberation collection
1941-2010
1970-1979
MS 1846
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
15.02
(28 boxes)
The Lesbian and Gay Liberation Collection includes publications and ephemera related to the lesbian and gay liberation movements, as well as material related to travel and the arts.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred by the Larry Kramer Initiative Executive Coordinator, 2004-2005. Transferred from the Librarian for Gay and Lesbian Studies, 2006-2007 and 2011. Gift of Frank Gagliardi, 2007. Transferred from the LGBT Co-Op, 2009.
Arrangement
The materials are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The Lesbian and Gay Liberation Collection includes publications and ephemera related to the lesbian and gay liberation movements, as well as material related to travel and the arts.
Gay liberation movement; Homosexuality; Lesbianism; LGBTQ resource
- Inventory, 1941-2004
  - 11" x 14" or smaller
    - Accomplices and Victims [Save Our Human Rights Foundation], undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - After Dark, vol. 12, nos. 1-2, 5-12; vol. 13, nos. 1-4; vol. 14, no. 3/4, 1979-1981 (Box 1, Folder 2 - 5)
    - Alix Dobkin's Adventures in Women's Music, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - "All Womens Dance", 1970 April 3 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Alliance to Stop Abusive Police, letter, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Amazon Quarterly, vol. 1, no. 1; vol. 1, no. 4/vol. 2, no. 1; vol. 3, no. 2, 1972-1975 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - American Civil Liberties Union
      - Above the Law: The Justice Department's War Against First Amendment, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Lesbian and Gay Rights Project Docket, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - ...And Justice for All... A Tribute to the March on Washington, D.C., October 11, 1987 [The William W. Wolfe Foundation], 1988 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - The Answer is Matriarchy [Barbara Love and Elizabeth Shanklin], 1978 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Ask No Man Pardon: The Philosophical Importance of Being Lesbian [Elsa Gidlow], 1975 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Assorted cards, flyers, stickers, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Backwater Babies [Guy Colwell], 1975 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Because Mourning Sickness is a Staple in my Country, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - The Beginner's Guide to Cruising [George Marshall], 1964 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - The Best of HI! [L. Craig Schoonmaker], 1979 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - The Better Dream House [Joe Dunn], 1968 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - The Bi-Monthly [The Bisexual Center], vol. 1, nos. 2-4, 6-vol. 3, no. 6-vol. 9, nos. 1, 3 and ephemera [2 issues are numbered vol. 3, no. 5], 1977-1985, undated (Box 2, Folder 20 - 22)
    - Boy With Arms Akimbo: His Story, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Breaking the Silence, Overcoming the Fear: Homophobia Education, Circa 1985 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - The Chicana Feminist [Martha P. Cotera], 1977 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Christopher Street, vol. 2, no. 4; vol. 4, no. 4, 1977 Oct, 1979 December (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Chrysalis
      - Nos. 1-4, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 26 - 27)
      - Nos. 5-10; vol. 2, no. 2, 1978-1979, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 28 - 30)
    - Citizens News, 2 issues [published by Strait and Associates], 1964, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - A Comparative Approach to the Meaning of Gay Liberation [David Bertelson; distributed by Gay Switchboard], 1970 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Compulsory Heterosexuality and Lesbian Existence [Adrienne Rich], 1980 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Connexions: An International Women's Quarterly, "Global Lesbianism," 2 issues, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Considerations in Therapy with Lesbian Clients, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Contacts Magazine, issue 1, 1993 February (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Contemplation [includes correspondence of 1976 Nov 7], undated (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Council on Religion and the Homosexual
      - Letter, Agatha Mathys to Governing Board, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - Report[s] of The Council on Religion and the Homosexual [Del Martin], 1964 (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - "HERE'S WHATREALLYHAPPENED--" [Committee for the Mardi Gras Ball], 1965 (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - A Brief of Injustices: An Indictment of Our Society in Its Treatment of the Homosexual [two versions], [1965?] (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - The Homosexual and the Church [Donald S. Lucas; published by The Mattachine Society], 1966 (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - Social Action, 34, no. 4, "Civil Liberties and Homosexuality", 1967 (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - CRH Newsletter, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - CRH: 1964/1968 (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - Refugees From America: A Gay Manifesto [Carl Wittman], 1970 (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - Symposium on Life-Styles of the Homosexual [flyer], 1973 (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - CRH Chronicle, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - The Church and the Homosexual, undated (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - Council on Religion and the Homosexual brochure, undated (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - Essays on Religion and the Homosexual, Volume 1 [published by Council on Religion and the Homosexual], undated (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - "Get Together" [flyer], undated (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - Homosexual Action Forum [flyer], undated (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - "Mailing List to Participants", undated (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - Administrative [includes "Goals and Purposes," by-laws, "Proposed Program," and minutes], 1961-1966, undated (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Cunt Coloring Book [Tee Corrine], [1988], 1997 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Daughters of Bilitis [short statement on orgins of name by unknown author], undated (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Day of Solidarity [Cuban revolution; poster], undated (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Eating Artichokes [Willyce Kim, Wendy Cadden], 1972 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Effeminism
      - A Conversation between Cy Schoenfield and Elijah [published by Student Research Facility], 1971 (Box 3, Folder 43)
      - On Offing Bullshit and Other Forms of Male Supremacy [ The Effeminist ], 1972 (Box 3, Folder 43)
      - Berkeley Resistance to Gay Organizers, Minority Mentality and Politics of False Promises: We Ain't Marching Anymore, undated (Box 3, Folder 43)
      - A Modest Proposal for Gay People's Liberation [Gay People's Projects/The Effeminist], undated (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Elysian Fields, Booksellers [catalogs], undated (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Encuentro Femenil, vol.1, no. 2, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Every Tenth Man [Mattachine Society], 1960 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Eye To Eye: Portraits of Lesbians [JEB], 1979 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - "Exodus International Conference Not Welcome in San Francisco", Undated (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Families [Linda Gordon], 1970 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - "Fat Oppression and Fat Liberation" [Judith Stein], [1980] (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - FAT?SO!, issue 1, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Federal Employment of Homosexual American Citizens [Mattachine Society of Washington, D.C.], 1965 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Feminary, vol. 10, no. 1-vol. 12, no. 1, 1979-1982 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Feminism in the 80's...Facing Down the Right [Charlotte Bunch], 1981 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Focus, 2 issues, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Friends of Darkover
      - The Darkover Newsletter, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 55)
      - Tales of the Free Amazons, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Frontiers, "Lesbian History Issue", 1979 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Gay Academic Union
      - "The Universities and the Gay Experience" conference proceedings, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 57)
      - Dangerous Trends in Feminism [John Lauritsen], 1976 (Box 4, Folder 57)
      - Gay Academic Union Newsletter, vol. 1, no. 1, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Gay Activists Alliance: 20 Questions about Homosexuality: A Political Primer, undated (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Gay Athletic Games I, program, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Gay Flames
      - Gay Consciousness, undated (Box 4, Folder 60)
      - 3rd World Gay Revolution, undated (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - "Gay Freedom Day 1978" program (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - "Gay Freedom Day 1979: How Free Are We?" flyer [Radical Women, The Freedom Socialist Party, Committee for a Revolutionary Socialist Party] (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - "Gay Freedom Day Parade and Celebration" program, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - Gay Insurgent: Journal of Gay Liberation Research, Reviews and News [formerly Midwest Gay Academic Journal ], 1979 (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - Gay Liberation [published by Red Butterfly], 1970 (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - Gay Liberation and Socialism: Documents from the Discussions on Gay Liberation Inside the Socialist Workers Party (1970-1973) [David Thorstad], 1976 (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - Gay Liberation and the Struggle for Socialism: A Socialist Workers Party Pamphlet [Noel Halifax], 1988 (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - "Gay Liberation Community Power and Sex" [statement by unknown author], undated (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - "Gay Liberation Day", 1975 (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - Gay Liberation Front [Washington, D.C.; letter announcing a boycott, and "Proposals for Organization"], 1970, undated (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - Gay Liberation Front Manifesto [London], 1971 (Box 4, Folder 71)
    - Gay Liberation Today, undated (Box 4, Folder 72)
    - The Gay Liberator [Gay Liberation Auckland (New Zealand)], 1974 (Box 4, Folder 73)
    - Gay New York Magazine, vol. 1, nos. 1-3; vol. 2, nos. 1, 3-4, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 74)
    - Gay Oppression and Liberation; or: Homophobia: Its Causes and Cure [Gay Theory Work Group of the Movement for a New Society], 1977 (Box 5, Folder 75)
    - A Gay Parent's Guide to Legal Custody [Anti-Sexism Committee of the San Francisco-Bay Area National Lawyer's Guild], 1980 (Box 5, Folder 76)
    - The Gay Picture Book, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 77)
    - Gay Pride and the Economic Crisis [Youth Against War and Fascism], 1975 (Box 5, Folder 78)
    - The Gay Question and Women's Oppression [Los Angeles Work Group, M-L], 1979 (Box 5, Folder 79)
    - Gay Sunshine
      - Gay Sunshine: A Journal of Gay Liberation, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 80)
      - Letter regarding editorial decisions/policies, undated (Box 5, Folder 80)
    - Gay Task Force of the American Library Association
      - Censored, Ignored, Overlooked. Too Expensive? How to Get Gay Materials into Libraries, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 81)
      - Feeding the Hungry Gay Bookworm [Barbara Gittings], undated (Box 5, Folder 81)
    - Gay Youth Community News [Gay Youth Community Coalition of the Bay Area], undated (Box 5, Folder 82)
    - Gayspeak [Joseph J. Hayes], 1976 (Box 5, Folder 83)
    - Goddess of Lesbian Dreams [Fran Winant], 1980 (Box 5, Folder 84)
    - "Groovy Guy '77" program [ The Advocate ], 1977 (Box 5, Folder 85)
    - Growing Up Gay [Youth Liberation pamphlet], 1976 (Box 5, Folder 86)
    - Guìa Legal Del Homosexual Urbano [Ernesto A. Martinez-Mexico], 1985 (Box 5, Folder 87)
    - H.Q., vol. 1, no. 1, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 88)
    - Hard Words and Why Lesbians Have to Say Them [Caroline Halliday, Sheila Shulman, and Caroline Griffin], 1979 (Box 5, Folder 89)
    - "Harvey Milk's Birthday 1982" program [Harvey Milk Gay Democratic Club] (Box 5, Folder 90)
    - Homophile Community Health Services, pamphlets, undated (Box 5, Folder 91)
    - The Homosexual Citizen, 1966 March (Box 5, Folder 91)
    - "Homosexual Unity and Conformity" [flyer], undated (Box 5, Folder 92)
    - Homosexuality [Alfred C. Kinsey], 1941 (Box 5, Folder 93)
    - Homosexuality and the Sickness Theory [Louis Crompton; London, England], 1969 (Box 5, Folder 94)
    - IKON, vol. 2, no. 1, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 95)
    - In Praise of Boys: Moorish Poems from Al-Andalus [translated by Erskine Lane], 1975 (Box 5, Folder 96)
    - In the Spirit of Stonewall [ Workers World reprint], 1979 (Box 5, Folder 97)
    - In Your Face, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 98)
    - Institute of Homophile Studies, catalogs, 1965-1966, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 99)
    - IALGAL Newsletter, issue 1 [International Association Of Lesbian and Gay Archives and Libraries], 1980 (Box 5, Folder 100)
    - International Lesbian/Gay Freedom Day Parade and Celebration [programs], 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 101)
    - Jean Genet [Tom Driver, Columbia Essays on Modern Writers], 1966 (Box 5, Folder 102)
    - The Khaki Closet [a Citizen Soldier handbook], 1992 (Box 5, Folder 103)
    - The Ladder, vol. 7, nos. 3, 5-6, and vol. 9, no. 4, 1962-1963, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 104)
    - Lavender and Red Union, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 105)
    - Lavender Papers 2: An Analysis of Lesbian Oppression [New York Women's School], 1975 (Box 5, Folder 106)
    - Legislative Guide to Gay Rights [Portland Town Council], 1976 (Box 5, Folder 107)
    - Lesbian and Gay Insurrection [LAGAI flyers], 1996, 1998, undated (Box 6, Folder 108)
    - Lesbian Ethics, vol. 1, no. 1-vol. 2, no. 3, 1984-1987 (Box 6, Folder 109)
    - Lesbian Feminist [Lesbian Feminist Liberation], 1976 (Box 6, Folder 110)
    - Lesbian Herstory Archives pamphlet, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 111)
    - Lesbian Mothers and Their Children: An Annotated Bibliography of Legal and Psychological Materials [Lesbian Rights Project], 1980 (Box 6, Folder 112)
    - A Lesbian Photo Album [Cathy Cade], 1987 (Box 6, Folder 113)
    - Lesbian Photography Directory [Morgan Greenwald], 1982 (Box 6, Folder 114)
    - The Lesbian Tide, vol. 1, no. 12, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 115)
    - Lesbianism: A Socialist Feminist Perspective [Susan Williams, a Radical Women publication], undated (Box 6, Folder 116)
    - Lesbians as we See Ourselves, 1975 June (Box 6, Folder 117)
    - Libera, nos. 1-2, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 118)
    - Los Angeles Advocate, vol. 2, no. 5, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 119)
    - Loving Women [the Nomadic Sisters], 1976 (Box 6, Folder 120)
    - Lucky, no. 1, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 121)
    - Magnus, nos. 1-2, 1976, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 122)
    - Making a Way: Lesbians Out Front [JEB], 1987 (Box 6, Folder 123)
    - "Man and Society," Journal of the Albany Trust, No. 10, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 123)
    - Margins, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 124)
    - Massachusetts, ephemera, 1974, undated (Box 6, Folder 125)
    - The Meaning of Gay Liberation [John F. Burnett], 1978 (Box 6, Folder 126)
    - The Meaning of Our Love for Women is What We Have Constantly to Expand [Adrienne Rich], 1977 June 26 (Box 6, Folder 127)
    - Mental Health and Gay Liberation [Ronald D. Lee], 1972 (Box 6, Folder 128)
    - Motive [Lesbian/Feminist issue by the Furies; Gay Men's Liberation issue], 1972 (Box 6, Folder 129)
    - National Association of Black and White Men Together, Quarterly, Vol. XI, No. 3, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 129)
    - National Gay and Lesbian Task Force [formerly National Gay Task Force]
      - Gay Parent's Support Packet, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 130)
      - Anti-Gay Violence, Victimization & Defamation in 1989 (Box 6, Folder 130)
    - The National Lesbian Health Care Survey [National Lesbian and Gay Health Foundation], 1988 (Box 7, Folder 131)
    - National March on Washington for Lesbian and Gay Rights [official souvenir program], 1979 October 14 (Box 7, Folder 132)
    - New York Gay Liberation Front ["article" on purpose], undated (Box 7, Folder 133)
    - New York Knight Life, vol. 1, no. 3; vol. 2, no. 6, 1979, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 134)
    - Notes from the Second Year: Women's Liberation: Major Writings of the Radical Feminists [Shulamith Firestone, Anne Koedt], 1970 (Box 7, Folder 135)
    - Notes from the Third Year: Women's Liberation [Shulamith Firestone, Anne Koedt], 1971 (Box 7, Folder 136)
    - One Confidential, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 137)
    - Open and Positive: An Account of How John Warburton Came Out at School and the Consequences [Gay Teacher's Group, London, England], undated (Box 7, Folder 138)
    - O.U.R. Lecture, Study and Research Group [Philip Clore], 1977 (Box 7, Folder 139)
    - OUT, vol. 1, no. 2, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 140)
    - OUTNY, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 140)
    - "Pastoral Letter on Sexual Ethics," Dignity Task Force on Sexual Ethics, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 140A)
    - PFLAG/Parents, Families, and Friends of Lesbians and Gays, pamphlets, 1994, 1999, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 140B)
    - "Photography by James Armstrong", 1974 (Box 7, Folder 141)
    - The Playbook for Women about Sex [Joani Blank], 1975 (Box 7, Folder 142)
    - Pointblank Times, vol. 3, no. 5, 1977 November (Box 7, Folder 143)
    - Pride Guide '84, 1984, 2002, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 144)
    - Psychiatry and the Homosexual: A Brief Analysis of Oppression [Gay Liberation pamphlet no. 1; London, England], 1973 (Box 7, Folder 145)
    - PURSUIT and Symposium, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 146)
    - Queer Nation
      - Queer Week [newsletter], 1990 (Box 7, Folder 147)
      - Assorted papers, undated (Box 7, Folder 148)
    - QueerNET News >, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 149)
    - "Queers Read This" ["I Hate Straights" pamphlet], 1990 (Box 7, Folder 150)
    - Religion
      - Christ and the Homosexual [Rev. Michael Francis], 1969 (Box 7, Folder 151)
      - Report on Homosexuality [Church of England Diocese of Sydney (Australia)], 1973 (Box 7, Folder 151)
      - Homosexual Catholics: A Primer for Discussion [Dignity], 1977 (Box 7, Folder 151)
    - Remember the Fire: Lesbian Sadomasochism in a Post Nazi-Holocaust World [Irene Reti], 1986 (Box 7, Folder 152)
    - The Rock: A Collection of Lesbian Expressions, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 153)
    - Rock Dreams [Guy Peellaert and Nik Cohn], 1973 (Box 7, Folder 154)
    - "Run Roberta Run" flyer, undated (Box 7, Folder 155)
    - Salsaworks: Resource Manual, 1984 September (Box 7, Folder 156)
    - Salt and Sage [Sacred Faerie Circle], 1994 (Box 7, Folder 157)
    - Sapphire, vol. 1, no. 1, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 158)
    - The Second Wave, vol. 1, no. 1, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 159)
    - Shirley Chisholm Speaks Out on Gay Minority Rights [presidential campaign brochure], undated (Box 8, Folder 160)
    - Sisters [Daughters of Bilitis], 1971-1975 (Box 8, Folder 161)
    - Society for Individual Rights
      - "Sirlebrity Capades of 1965 program (Box 8, Folder 162)
      - Specific Immediate Realizable: 1972 Directional Report (Box 8, Folder 162)
      - Happy Birthday! Special Edition [newsletter], 1974 (Box 8, Folder 163)
    - Some Reflections on Separatism and Power [Marilyn Frye], 1977 (Box 8, Folder 164)
    - Sports and the Macho Male [John Mitzel], [1973],1976 (Box 8, Folder 165)
    - "Statement of the Male Homosexual Workshop", undated (Box 8, Folder 166)
    - Stefan de Jaeger, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 167)
    - Tangents, vol. 2, no. 6; vol. 3, no. 11/12, 1968, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 168)
    - Task Force on Homosexuality: Final Report and Background Papers [National Institute of Mental Health; U.S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare; reprint], 1976 (Box 8, Folder 169)
    - Town Talk, 5 issues, 1964-1966 (Box 8, Folder 170)
    - Vector Index [list of advertisers], 1971 (Box 8, Folder 171)
    - We Are All Androgynous Yellow [Bob Mellors; London, Engand], 1980 (Box 8, Folder 172)
    - We Were There! [John Wieners; Good Gay Poets], [1972] (Box 8, Folder 173)
    - Welfare Rights Handbook, 1971 September (Box 8, Folder 174)
    - "Why I Hated the March on Washington" pamphlet [QUASH], undated (Box 8, Folder 175)
    - WIN [peace and freedom through nonviolent action], 1969 (Box 8, Folder 176)
    - Woman to Woman, 2nd ed. [S.C.U.M.], undated (Box 8, Folder 177)
    - Women: A Journal of Liberation, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 178)
    - Women's Sexuality: Myth and Reality [Kass Demeter/Teeters], 1977 (Box 8, Folder 179)
  - Oversize
    - Citizens News, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 180)
    - Cruise News and World Report, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 181)
    - Crusader, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 182)
    - Effeminist, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 183)
    - Gay Forum, vol. 1, nos. 3-5, 1971, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 184)
    - Gay Freedom Celebration, 1974-1975, undated (Box 9, Folder 185)
    - Gay Freedom Day, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 186)
    - Gay Power, vol. 1. nos. 1, 3, 9, undated (Box 9, Folder 187)
    - Gay Pride [San Francisco], 1972 (Box 9, Folder 188)
    - Ginger and Spice, vol. 2, no. 1, [1973] (Box 9, Folder 189)
    - International Lesbian and Gay Freedom Day, 1983-1985 (Box 9, Folder 190 - 192)
    - Kalendar, vol. 2, issues B7, B17, B21, B26; vol. 3, issues B24, G3, G4-G9, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 193 - 196)
    - Lavender Vision, undated (Box 9, Folder 197)
    - Lesbian Insider/Insighter/Inciter, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 198)
    - New Haven Advocate, "Gay Pride", 2004 (Box 9, Folder 199)
    - Newswest, 19 issues including vol. 1, nos. 2-20, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 200 - 204)
    - Nós [Portugal], 1980 (Box 10, Folder 205)
    - On Parade, 3 issues, 1981, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 206)
    - Oracle of the Gay Emmaus House, 3 issues including nos. 1, 3, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 207)
    - OUT!, no. 1, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 208)
    - "Rally" [Armed Forces Protest], 1966 (Box 10, Folder 209)
    - San Francisco Free Press, vol. 1, nos. 3-9, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 210)
    - "Sex and Justice: The Anita Hill/Clarence Thomas Hearings" [poster], [1993] (Box 10, Folder 211)
    - The Voice [Gay Students Coalition], 1974 (Box 10, Folder 212)
- Additional material, 1969-2005; 1969-1981; Accession 2006-M-065
  - After Touch [Jan Clausen], 1975 (Box 1)
  - Amazon Odyssey [Ti-Grace Atkinson], 1974 (Box 1)
  - Amazon Quarterly, vol. 1, issue 2; vol. 2, issue 2-vol. 3, issue 1, 1973-1974 (Box 1)
  - The Answer is Matriarchy [Barbara Love and Elizabeth Shanklin], undated (Box 1)
  - APHRA, vol. 4, no. 4, 1973 fall (Box 1)
  - AZALEA, vol. 3, no. 3; vol. 4, nos. 1-2; vol. 5, no. 1, 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Boston Women's Poetry Anthology, 1970 December (Box 1)
  - Burn This and Memorize Yourself, undated (Box 1)
  - Come Out!, 1970 (Box 1)
  - ComingOutRage, issue 1, 1973 May (Box 1)
  - The Common Woman, issue 1, 1973 winter (Box 1)
  - Considerations in Therapy with Lesbian Clients, 1979 (Box 1)
  - Cowrie, vol. 1, nos. 2-3, 5; vol. 2, nos. 1, 3, 1973-1974 (Box 1)
  - Crossing the DMZ [Martha Shelley], 1974 (Box 1)
  - Dear Sky [Susan Griffin; 2 versions], 1971, 1973 (Box 1)
  - Dyke Jacket [Fran Winant], 1976 (Box 1)
  - Dyke Shorts [Mary Wings], 1978 (Box 1)
  - "The Earliest Gay Pickets: When, Where, Why" [Barbara Gittings], 2005 January (Box 1)
  - Earth Rites, vols. 1-2, 1978 (Box 2)
  - Eating Artichokes, 1972 (Box 2)
  - Families [Linda Gordon], 1970 (Box 2)
  - Feminary, vol. 11, no.1/2, 1980 (Box 2)
  - "Feminist Therapy with Lesbians and Other Women," Homosexual Counseling Journal [Jean Mundy], 1974 October (Box 2)
  - The First Elizabethan Coloring Book, 1980 (Box 2)
  - Flannel Morning (Love Songs for Dr. V) [Sonya Jones], 1977 (Box 2)
  - Free Our Sisters, 1975 (Box 2)
  - Fresh-Roasted Peanuts [Vicki Hudspith], 1976 (Box 2)
  - "Gay Liberation Front-Political Orientation Reading List #1", undated (Box 2)
  - "Gays in Library Land" [Barbara Gittings], 1990 (Box 2)
  - Gays on Campus [J. Lee Lehman], 1975 (Box 2)
  - Homosexuality and the Sickness Theory [Louis Crompton], 1969 (Box 2)
  - I Am Not a Careful Poet [Wendy Stevens], 1975 (Box 2)
  - I Know You Know, vol. 1, nos. 1-2, 4, 6; vol. 2, no. 1, 1984-1985 (Box 2)
  - Join Hands, nos. 1-3, 6-8, 10-12, 1976-1977, undated (Box 2)
  - Journey [Martha Courtot], 1977 (Box 2)
  - Journeys on the Living [Lynda Koolish], 1973 (Box 2)
  - The Ladder, vol. 16, nos. 5/6-7/8, 11/12, 1972 (Box 2)
  - Lady-Unique-Inclination-of-the-Night, cycle 1, 1976 fall (Box 2)
  - A Legal Guide for Gay and Lesbian Couples [Hayden Curry and Denis Clifford], 1980 (Box 2)
  - Lesbian Photography Directory [Morgan Gwenwald], 1982 (Box 2)
  - The Lesbian Tide [briefly known as The Tide ], vol. 2, nos. 7-10/11; vol. 3, no. 1-vol. 5, no. 2; vol. 6, no. 1-vol. 9, no. 6, 1973-1980 (Box 3)
  - Lesbian Voices, vol. 1, no. 3; vol. 2, nos. 1-2, 4, vol. 3, nos. 1-4, 1975-1978, undated (Box 4)